# Viacheslav Korbut

# Junior (Trainee) developer

#### SUMMARY

"I am a Java Developer with comprehensive knowledge and practical experience in Java programming gained through the Java Developer course. Skilled in Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), Java application development, and proficiency in the Java Enterprise Edition (JEE) stack and related technologies. Strong problem-solving skills and a passion for coding."

## SKILLS

Java Core

JUnit

Java Collections API

Hibernate

Spring Boot

Database(PostgreSQL, MySQL)

Spring MVC

Build systems and dependencies

(Gradle, Maven)

Spring Security

GIT(GitHub)

#### **EDUCATION**

Master of Arts at NTU "Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute"

2008-2014

# ADDITIONAL COURSES AND TRAININGS

Java Pro at Hillel IT School

2022

https://certificate.ithillel.ua/view/53433171

• Java Enterprise at Hillel IT School

2023

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Design Engineer at GRAND

2020 - present

At GRAND company, I am engaged in transporting RIB boats. I design frames and stacks for their transportation by sea containers and land trucks.

• Design Engineer at Electrovazhmash

2013-2020

At Electrovazhmash plant, I was involved in developing innovative products and mechanisms to facilitate the fastening and transportation of parts of the company's turbo generators, hydro generators, and large direct current machines. I participated in the development of a prototype for an experimental frame for moving large cargo around the plant. I developed a large number of structural frames for moving large units and parts.

## новву

Java and my family.



#### CONTACTS

Location

Kharkiv, Kharkiv Oblast, Ukraine

✓ Will consider relocation

Email

minowaman777@gmail.com

Phone

+380630517137

Telegram

https://t.me/korbut viacheslav

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/viacheslav-korbut-5742a1272/

GitHul

https://github.com/KorbutViacheslav

## LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian C2
- English B1